

ZIVILE KAIRYTE

Marketing & Communications Professional

zikairyte@gmail.com

+32 499 155143

www.zivile.be

Brussels, Belgium

SKILLS

Omnichannel marketing: Field marketing, Content marketing, Marketing materials,

Design:

ABM

Adobe Illustrator, Adobe XD Adobe Photoshop, Canva, Figma

Advertising:

LinkedIn ads, Google Analytics GA4, Google Ads, Email marketing

Website:

WordPress, Joomla, Odoo Buffer, Hootsuite, Loomly HTML & CSS. SEO & SEA

AI & Automation Tools Chat GPT, Midjourney, Writesonic

LANGUAGES

Lithuanian ● ● ●

English

French $\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ \circ$

Dutch •0000

EDUCATION

Master in Marketing Management Vilnius University (2017-2018)

Bachelor in International Business and Communication ISM University of Management and Economics (2011-2015)

CERTIFICATIONS

Web design UX/UI (2019) Vilnius coding school

Google Ads (2024) Reseau Formation

HOBBIES

Tennis, Roller skating Kitesurfing, Snowboarding Reading serious and not serious books, Drawing

SUMMARY

Digital marketing & communications professional with 6+ years' experience in startups & international organizations. Skilled in website management, social media, email campaigns, and content strategy with a focus on clear messaging and agile project delivery, marketing materials, and targeted campaigns for B2B and B2C sectors.

EXPERIENCE

Marketing and Communications Freelancer

2024.10- Ongoing Europe

Marketing projects with internationally working B2B and B2C companies

- Communication strategy for key accounts, content creation, emails.
- Creating sales enablement materials.

Communications Manager

2021.06 - 2023.11 Brussels, Belgium

A European association working with +900 CPG companies including Unilever, P&G, Henkel, Reckitt, EU institutions and national associations. Reported directly to Communications Director and managed budget of the projects.

- Developed content campaigns tailored to target audiences.
- Created marketing materials (presentations, one-pagers, case studies) for marketing campaigns.
- Responsible for account based marketing campaigns (lead acquisition, events, webinars, email marketing and socials), achieving 30% annual audience growth.
- Analysed market trends, competitors, and industry to support strategic communication initiatives.
- Organized training programs (workshops, interactive sessions) for CPGs, national associations.
- Facilitated sustainability initiatives within Henkel, Reckitt, P&G, and Unilever across Europe.
- Organised events for key stakeholders (European Commission, CPG companies, and policymakers).

Commissioner Cabinet BlueBook Trainee

European Commission, Commissioner's Sinkeviciaus Cabinet

2020.02 - 2021.02 Brussels, Belgium

Commissioner's Sinkevicius cabinet covers these topics: Circular Economy, Chemicals Strategy for Sustainability, Hydrogen Strategy, Biodiversity Strategy. Reported directly to the Head of Cabinet.

- External communications: articles, supporting events organisation.
- Internal communications: research based weekly briefings for internal teams materials and briefing packs for decision-makers.
- Supported outreach to policymakers and ministries on sustainability and circular economy.

Marketing Executive

Lvmpo.io

2017.07 - 2018.07 Vilnius. Lithuania

Lympo is a blockchain startup promoting healthy sports habits. As part of the core team, I helped raise \$12 million through crowdfunding. Reported directly to the CEO.

- Created and maintained Lympo.lt's brand strategy to boost awareness and lead generation.
- Developed and executed comprehensive marketing activities for growth and engagement.
- Managed a thriving community of 12,000 active members globally for Lympo.io.
- Set up email marketing campaigns and improved CTR 20%.
- Led the development of the Lympo.lt website.
- Managed a partnership with Lithuania's largest gym chain.
- Organised physical and online events for Lympo.lt platform users.
- Managed creative agencies to ensure consistent and impactful messaging and positioning.

Social Media Marketing Executive

2018.01 - 2018.06

Global

Cryptonews.com

A platform covering the latest trends, news, and developments in the crypto industry. Reported to the Project Manager. Achieved a 27% increase in social media growth, 10% engagement with no additional

Established and developed the social media presence, driving audience growth and engagement.

budget.

- Developed and executed a targeted social media strategy to boost engagement.
- Managed copywriters and graphic designers, ensuring consistent content delivery.